all right it's tuesday january 26 2016
omnibus fas est MMXVI XXVI Martis January
and hear the stories were covering this
fusi iacebant in historias et audite hoc
week vtech learning lodge applications
vtech week doctrina sua hospitari valeant applications
are back online following November's
November haec autem reversus est scriptor online
hack attack which exposed millions of
Morbi impetum exposita trucidabunt
children's or smoke information nests
habitent filii indicio fumum
thermostats have been leaking users VIP
thermostats stillante portasse users sunt VIP
codes raising real concerns over
de codicibus per vera raising
Internet of Things developers and how
Developers et quomodo Internet Rerum
they're approaching security it's also
ipsi erant 'suus' etiam accessus securitatem
been found that media devices sold to
inventa quae media cogitationes venundati
several government offices have hidden
imperium pluribus officiis et occultatum
back doors with sniffing functions and
reversusque portas tecum munera, et capit cujuscunque cocturae
Google is going to be paying 130 million
CXXX million reddens est iens ut Google
pounds in back taxes in Britain an
in Britannia reversus est in libris tributa
independent half-life game has been
dimidium-vita independens ludum fuit
approved by valve yes and it's coming
probatus per valvae, et quod sic suus 'venire
soon it's written by a guy who quit his
cum suus 'a guy qui scripsit in quit
job to create the game that's dedication
creare ludum quod suus 'officium dedication
and remember that dad whose son ran up
memento quod et pater quorum filii procurrens
the xbox bill for more than eight
libellum pro xbox quam octo
thousand dollars we've got an update on
Comperto Status ad centena
that story tonight and these stories are
hac fabula quae narrantur
coming right up so don't go away you've
ut in ius venire non auferetur tibi Ive '
got mad skills now hone them learn new
iam got demens acuunt eorum artes discere novum
skills or improve your existing ones
aut amplio vestri solers entibus
with online video tutorials and training
with online video tutorials et educatio
from Linda calm through our special link
leniret, per nostram ex Maria peculiarem
at cat five dot TV / Linda learn
cat ad apicem quinque TV / Cornelius discite
software technology creative and
partum, et technology software
business skills you can use today to
negotium solers potes uti et hodie
help you achieve your professional goals
auxilium vobis consequi tua metas professional
join today and start learning will give
hodie et dabit satus discendi copulare
you this chance to try it absolutely
hoc casu est omnino vobis temptare
free with unlimited access to all of the
liber cum illimitata accessum ad omnes
courses sign up now for free cat5 dot TV
Nunc cursus subscribere sursum pro CAT5 dat liberam TV
/ linda jeff weston and here are the
/ Linda Jeff Weston 'et hie est
stories we're coming from the category 5
genus fabulas erant ex V
TV news room chill children's toy from
TV locus nuntium gelidus natorum a toy
VTech has reopened key functions of its
Rursum fodit alios VTech habet clavem munera eius
learning lodge gate where a gateway for
quo cognito cellulam porta ad portam
the first time since it was hacked in
ex quo primum in laceratus
November 2015 the online saw a service
November MMXV et vidi servitium online
for as a portal for customers to
et in pretium ad portal
download games ebooks other content on
contentus de aliis ludos download ebooks
vtec devices they can now register
register now possunt cogitationes VTEC
manage their accounts and use the app
app uti ratione atque administrare
store but some of the products including
thesaurizate autem quidam products a comprehendo
the power extra laptop and ino TV remain
laptop TV manet extra potestatem et ino
offline almost 6.4 million children's
fere 6.4 million liberi online scriptor
details were exposed by a hacker and
expositae sunt, et singula a Piratica
of those products which remain offline
quod eorum products manere offline
they include secret safe diary selfie
in quibus salvus secretum commentarius selfie
which is so ironic that it was hacked
et abscidi eam quae irrisorie
and released snuggle and sleep musical
et dimisit snuggle musicis et fugit
sheep and mobigo touch learning system
ac ratio litterarum MobiGo tactus
Alan Wong is v-tex chairman and the
Wong sit Alan v tex-Praesidem, et
group chief executive and he said in a
in summum exsecutiva coetus, et ait:
statement after the cyberattack we have
dicitur post habemus cyberattack
focused on further strengthening
porro focused in confirmatione
security around our user registration
securitas circa user adnotatione nostri
information and other services within
servicia et alia notitia in
learning lodge mr. Wang goes on to warn
cognito cellulam metus. Secutus fueris Wang
customers that they need to update their
mos postulo ut update eorum
learning lodge password as soon as
disciplina password ut maneamus
possible vtech is now confirmed that the
Nunc confirmata est possibile vtech
data access by the hacker include
obvius notitia includit a Piratica
children's names dates of birth and
nomina filiorum tempora nativitatis
gender as well as the name email address
tum genus nominis inscriptio
encrypted passwords secret question and
Tesserae occulto quaestionem Encrypted
answer for password retrieval IP address
IP oratio ad respondendum password retrieval
mailing address and download history of
et Mailing inscriptio download historia
the account holder well as I'm reading
propter quod ego legere atque possessor
this I'm starting to think I need to
Ego puto hoc incipiens ad ad opus
check that out because I'm pretty sure
Im 'pulchellus certus ut reprehendo sicco quod
we had the vtec product from our kids
habuimus enim de productum VTEC haedos
room did you have that crazy selfie
nonne tibi insanus, qui locus selfie
thing I did out of the selfie we had no
res egi de selfie non habuimus
they were like a little handheld device
parum notae fuerunt orci
I forget what they're kinda register for
Quia pius es subcriptio quod non obliviscar
it yeah because you download games so
yeah eo quod ludos ut download
hmm that's a scary thing and do you do
hmm aliquid quod suus 'FORMIDULOSUS et facitis
allow your kids to enter their real
permittit haedos ad veram
private information online well that's
privata notitia online bene ut '
the funny thing is I don't remember
rem ridiculam et est non recordabor
registering anything about my kids other
quod perscriptum de aliis haedos
than a profile that just had their name
quod est figura habens nomen
right what all of my information was on
quod ius informationes fui in omnibus angustiis meis
there sure so I don't know maybe people
certus ut illic maybe qui nescio
think I'm a kid I act like it sometimes
puto me tibi hedum de capris unum agit ut eum numquam
but I don't know still I'm thinking
sed usque non ego cogito
gotta go gotta go check this out but
Redditus autem hoc ire pergam reprehendo Redditus
it's interesting if I was part of that I
Si suus 'interesting pars ego sum
didn't get an email letting me know so
non tantum an email ut sciam ego intellegam
maybe I'm safe this is your note this is
maybe Im 'tutum hic tibi nota est: id
your notice you're watching category
notitiam tuam tu vigilantes genus
five and now you know change your
scitis autem et quinque tui quandoque
password that's reckon I can't use that
Existimo enim est scriptor password ut dixi, non potest utor
generic God that people used to use in
Dei, quod est in genere uti solebat,
the 80s for password or password 123
80s password in password CXXIII
password 123 oh that goes my email you
Quis autem est CXXIII ignoro My
know what it really infuriates me about
vere scio quod ita furit mihi
this is that i was really hoping to use
hoc est, ut ego utor innoxiis Antiatibus indici sperans
an innotab 3s personally the pic now
Nunc sit innotab 3s personaliter Pic
yeah the pink one and now I just don't
yeah in unum et rosea, non iustus nunc
know if I can try
si potero experiri
that well maybe we'll find something for
bene maybe nos quod youll 'reperio aliquid
you guys right bottom ba nest labs hope
Labs nidum spei fundamentum ius ba guys
to spark an Internet of Things
Præterea Synodus etiam Internet Rerum
revolution with the introduction of the
Cum introductio in revolution
Nest Learning Thermostat and after all
Doctrina nidum thermostat, post omnes,
many homeowners had never encountered a
Multi homeowners non offendit
thermostat that was so adept at
adeo Thermostat capacissimum
maintaining heat cooling levels using a
frigefaciendo sentiunt calorem usus tenebant levels
bevy of sensors and software magic while
totumque sororum sensoriis et magicae in software
shutting off when you left the room and
Cumque cubiculum de cludere
turning back on when you returned and
Cumque reversi terga vertentes
while no one expects that a nest
nemo speret nidum
thermostat should be locked down for
clausum fuerit pro Thermostat
security purposes maybe like a cell
ut a securitate proposita maybe cellulam
phone would be you would at least assume
telephonum id certe futurum sit apud te
that it wouldn't leak out personal
quod non alio emanauere
information of the homeowners however
sed de notitia in homeowners
two researchers from Princeton center of
Inquisitores de medio duorum Princeton
information technology policy PhD
consilium notitia technology PhD
student sarf hack grover and fellow roya
sarf studiosum ac saginantur grover conservis roya
and safe and sif I'd watched that one
Et observabant ut essem incolumis sif
yeah you know sorry about that I could
yeah quia contristati estis ut possem
have just said that the two tube the
et dixerunt, quod duo tantum tubo
folks from the school yeah you let the
Yeah turpis sem a dimisistis
HD students this is like an ongoing
HD ut alumni hoc requirit perennem
thing he throws these really difficult
vere difficilis haec res iacit
things to say in the news because he's
quae ad nuntium dicens quod suus '
just to trip me up the chat room loves
modo ad chat cubiculum scandali qui diligit me
it it's how I can just see it's how I
quod suus 'iustus videre quomodo possum quam quod suus'
can tell if you practiced yeah there was
Si autem scit memini exercitati
no practicing this is Ho natural news
o nuntium haec naturalia non practicing
right there you go this is this is it
hoc est quod tu recte
folks just throwing them into it anyway
mox coniectis in sem usquam
those guys that I can't pronounce
quod illis guys potest pronunciare
discovered that nest thermostats were
nidus erat compertum Thermostats
actually putting out the home zip code
exstinctis zip code vere est in domum suam
and as a result of the closest weather
et quasi tempestas propter arctissimam
station of its users nest acknowledged
de statione ad users recognovit posueris nidum tuum
that this was a bug in its thermostat
hoc erat in ugbay thermostat
software I was not an intentional act
software eram non intentionale
Google quickly fixed the issue while
Et confestim stetit fluxus certum Google
something is insidious as a zip code is
quod est insidiosa in zip code quod
relatively harmless in the grand scheme
se innoxium in grandi rationem
of things you know compared to like vtec
quae non novit, prae similis ei de VTEC
releasing all of your kids information
releasing omnes informationes vestris haedos
the lacs programming could lead to even
posset etiam ad lacs vestibulum
more serious privacy leaks the Internet
Internet potius effluat secretum gravis
of Things represents just another attack
altero autem modo repraesentat
vector for malicious parties to track
Vector malicious partes ad to track
your every move and even when you think
licet tu creasti omne
you're safe and secure in your own home
tibi saluus et securus de sua patria tua
it's up to tech companies to secure
suus 'usque ad tech turmas secure
customer data and for the things and
et quæ data est elit et
look and from the look of things they
quae ex vultu respicere
still have a long way to go and it's
Adhuc enim longum iter quod suus '
interesting i was chatting with a friend
amicus i fabulamur amet
of mine yesterday in a coffee shop and
in capulus tabernam et heri meus
he's like oh dude I've got this nest
quod suus 'got ut venias Ego Dudus istius nidi
thermostat I love it it's great talked
thermostat amo ut suus 'magnum loquebatur
all about it I'm thinking hey this is
quia cogitabat de omnibus heus Im 'hoc est,
kind of cool i might have to check that
frigus non posset esse genus sisto
out
de
and now I'm finding out that everybody
et nunc sum, ut omnes excogitato
knows where he lives yeah I i think
Yeah puto te scire ubi sit
there's this i think that's an
Puto quod illic 'hoc est
interesting point that you make that
interesting puncto, ut faciam tibi
really companies if you're going to make
Si vos erant 'iens ut realiter societates
this stuff connected you got to think
ista quae adfers cogitare
about security absolutely and maybe
de absolute securitatem et maybe
regular encryption is not good enough
non satis iusta Encryption
like this stuff should not be leaked
sic ut non leaked supellectilem
well it's funny because going into the
Bene suus 'ridiculam quia in eo
next news story it just intensifies that
Accedit, quod tunc solum est nuntium narratio
need for proper security and as we go
opus enim propriis ut securitate et vade
with everything digital there's more and
illic 'magis ac cum omnibus digital
more opportunities for the really smart
dolor magis occasiones ad rem
hackers and crackers and also people
hackers et fragor et populum
with malicious intent to gather this
defexit publico est mihi colligere hanc
information and unless you're the best
nisi notitia: et tu optimus
of the best of the best chances are
ex optimis optimus casus
somebody's going to find a way around it
quis suus 'iens ut circuitu esse viam inveniam
you know so companies need to wise up
scitis autem et societates necesse sapienti
and not just put out this product which
posuit et non solum productum ex hoc quod
is it can't be an afterthought it can't
hoc autem non potest esse retractu
be an afterthought I mean that should
ut si dico retractu
not happen and maybe the zip codes as
quod fieri fortasse zip code
you say or not him that narrows things
qui dicis non contrahit quæ vel
down pretty close but still I mean if it
et tamen dico quod sinus prope
monitors when you go and all that kind
et illa quando ingredieris monitores
of stuff maybe there's some way that by
et supellectilem maybe suus 'non ut aliquid ex
using your zip code they can find all
per vestram zip code quod invenire omnes
there's only three years in sorry get
illic 'tantum adepto contristati tribus annis
the IP suddenly the fun oh you're not
Non statim o amet IP
home boom digital home invasions mmm or
digital domum BUTIO in domum incursibus aut mmm
maybe that's a stretch maybe it's not
quod maybe suus 'non maybe suus' a proten
but still and with that thought in mind
adhuc autem et animam in isto animo
that X story Oh a company that supplies
O historia X, qui de turba autem administrat
audio-visual and building control
audio-visual et imperium aedificium
equipment to the US Army the White House
apparatu ad US Domus Alba Exercitus
and other security conscious
et alia securitate conscious
organizations built a deliberately
organizations built deliberate
concealed back door into dozens of its
quod in postico justo latet
products that could possibly be used to
products quod potest contingere posse, ut solebat,
hack or spy on users this is what
et trucidabunt exploratorem in hoc quod users
security researchers have said oh we're
o securitas dicti Inquisitores enim sumus
talking about this one members of
de his autem membra
austria-based security firm SEC consult
Austria, secundum securitatem firm consuleret SEC
said that they discovered a backdoor
dicitur quod agnoscebant sinum vero pseudothyrum
after analyzing the AMX n x 1200 it's a
secundum illud examinare AMX nx MCC
programmable programmable device used to
programmable programmable fabrica solebat,
control AV and building systems the
imperium aedificium systems ad AV,
researchers first became suspicious
Inquisitores ante suspectum est
after accounting a function called set
post munus dicitur a paro accounting
up subtle user account not a subtle name
Non subtili nomen usoris acute
yeah which is ironic well anyway so this
hoc est verbum per ironiam, quae usquam tam yeah
account it added highly privileged
Ideo addidit multum privilegiata
account with a hard-coded password to
Quamobrem durus Turcopolis password
the list of users authorized to login
AD auctoritate in album of users
unlike most of the other accounts this
dissimilis potissimum rationes ad hoc se
one had the ability to
qui potuit
capture the data packets that we're
ut sis facis capere notitia
flowing between the device and the
et fluit inter fabrica
network it was connected to the
quod ipsum coniunctum
researcher said someone with knowledge
dictum inquisitorem aliquo cognoscente
of the back door could completely
per posticum posset omnino
reconfigure and take over the device and
et quod reconfigure ut in fabrica
due to the highest privileges also start
et ex summo iure incipere
sniffing attacks from within the network
impetus a network in suae adtraxit
segment okay hold on let's be clear
segmentum scriptor Bene obtinuit patebit
about this these are benign benign
hae almae huius almae
multimedia devices so as music players
et ut musica inventa multimedia players
right things like that that are
quae huiusmodi ius
connected to government networks yes and
sic et retiacula coniuncta ad imperium
can sniff the data being passed through
in homine obvio forte possit notitia quod Transierunt
those networks yes let me continue I
sic ego continue retiacula ea me
never get back to this because this is
Numquam ad hoc quod haec est
like yeah right up my alley anyway the
yeah sicut ius meum in angustiis usquam
tell-tale function not only equips the
indica-fabula non solum munus instruit
account with packet sniffing
et ideo packet suae adtraxit
capabilities it also contains code that
hoc quoque codice, quod capabilities habet
prevents it from displaying when a list
quid impediat, ut propono album cum
of valid user names is enumerated like
user nomen ut verum ex non numeratur
talk about hey I'm here but you can't
sed heus tu me hic non loqui
find me coding so when sec consult
coding et invenietis, cum me consule sec
informed amx officials of the back door
AMX magistratus informari de retro ostium
last March we're going 2015 like a year
Martii anno ultimo erant 'iens ut MMXV
ago the equipment maker responded seven
factorem respondit septem abhinc apparatu
months later with an update that
post menses cum hoc update
acclaimed fixed the problem but in fact
Appellato forsit fuisset, sed eo
according to SEC console the update
SEC secundum consolabas update
merely changed the user name assigned to
mutata modo usor cum nomine assignata
the back door from Black Widow to I am
Nigrum vidua non sum et a tergo ostium
Batman Wow yes guys are great at
SPECULATOR Wow guys sunt sic magnae ad
obfuscation it's incredible I'm gonna
Im 'agnus dei obfuscation suus' incredibiliter
hack a bank and use a program called
et trucidabunt in ripam vocavit progressio utor a
hack a bank and yeah and they'll never
Gaudete et mensam et trucidabunt Numquam
figure it out because I am Batman anyway
instar is sicco SPECULATOR: quia ego usquam
so they changed the username but the
ita mutavit et nomen usoris
backdoor account and the capabilities
rationis facultatem pseudothyrum
built into it we're all there they
omnes qui erant in ea et extruxerunt
remain so amx has since released a
so remain est quia dimisit AMX
statement claiming that the accounts
dicitur quod rationes dicens
were used for diagnostics and
et quia usus sunt diagnostic
maintenance for computer support of
computatrum sustentationem et auxilium
technical issues okay I'm a huge Tom
Im 'okay ingens Tom technica exitibus
Clancy Fame I read his books love the
Fama suis libris lego amat Clancy
military stuff I play the game I do play
Ego ludere ludum et ludo supellectilem militum I
the game I just finished reading threat
EGO iustus consummavi ludum legere comminatione
vector which came out in 2009 you can
ex quo factum est in MMIX potes vector
buy that through our amazon link it's
buy ut suus 'in nostrum amazon link
true it's true but the whole premise of
omnis propositio vera est verum
the threat
in comminatione
vector plotline yeah is that China
yeah, quod vector plotline Sina
created a uploading virus so to speak to
uploading virum creata est, ut ita dicam,
benign media devices IE USB would be a
III USB ut esset inventa media benignae
good example would be your your home
esset bonum exemplum tuo in domum tuam
router yeah exactly and what would
et quod prorsus vellet iter itineris yeah
happen is it embedded in the actual code
ea fato fieri sit ipsa embedded in codice
like the ones and zeros of the device
sicut ones et ex zeros fabrica
that allowed it to connect to the
licet illud quod est ad coniungere
servers in the Chinese government which
Chinese regimen qui in servers
then sis's fiction this is fiction yeah
ra et s ficta haec ficta yeah
but it then gave them access to the
sed tunc dedit aditum
computer like they broke into the NSA
irrumpunt, ut computatrum ad NSA
they broke into the CIA they got
CIA nocte inrupit in
everything whatever people did on the
quicquid in populo
computer they found out they used it to
illi usus sunt computatrum adinvenit eam
manipulate them into working for the
adque ad flectere
Chinese government to sell secrets this
Chinese regimen vendere mysterium hoc
is the plot line at reading this new
insidiamini est rectam ad hoc legere
story going on by contrast to that
Aliquam ut pergeret contra
fictional story the news story this
poetica narratio historia ad nuntium haec
evening is nonfiction yeah this is real
haec vespera est ipsa nonfiction yeah
life but that was a plot line in a book
sed quod anima esset de insidiis quas recta in libro
2009 you know and now we're hearing
MMIX erant et nunc scio te audiunt
about it in actual news in 2016 I'm go
apud ipsam nuntium de eo in MMXVI ego vado
chicken and egg exacted did somebody
et fecit ovo gallinaceo quis interrogandus
read that book and get a great idea I
illo libro legitur et a magna idea essem
don't know say is it's here I know
scimus quia hic est dicere quod non irrumabo
I'm Batman watch out for Bruce Wayne but
SPECULATOR ad me vigilare de Brus, sed Wayne
no but this is serious stuff yeah first
Non autem hoc est prius et serium pulchritudine yeah
absolutely blows my mind that's
omnino spirat animus ut '
frightening hey I'm gonna calm down our
heus Im 'agnus dei nostri leniret et horribilis
I'm gonna have an end yeah he's cool I
Im 'agnus dei se habere finem yeah suus frigus me
don't do that not not today yeah all
nec non hodie, non facere omnia yeah
right google has agreed to pay 139
inter quae ius reddere CXXXIX Google
million pounds in back taxes after an
decies libras in tributa postquam reversus est
open audit of its accounts by the UK tax
et per rationes ex aperto audit tributum UK
authorities the payment covers money
auctoritatem pecuniae mercede operis sui
owed since twenty 2005 and follows a
Sequitur enim et viginti deberi MMV
six-year inquiry by Her Majesty's
Regiam majestatem inquisitionis per sex annos scriptor
Revenue and Customs and Google is one of
Consuetudines et vectigal et Google est unum
several multinational companies to have
ut pluribus societatibus multinational
been accused of avoiding tax in spite of
accusatus est apud tributum omnibus avoiding
making billions of pounds of sales in
Sales in libris faciendi billions
Britain senior figures at the u.s.
Britannia figuras senior in nobis
research giant said it would follow new
New research sequi se dixit giant
rules which would see it pay more taxes
reddere ea, quae videantur esse plura praecepta tributa
in the future ok I don't want to talk
ok nolo loqui in posterum
too much about tax evasion but billions
sed nimium billions de tributum elabi
of pounds in revenue that he'd pay taxes
libras dare tributum Caesari an vellem autem esse apud reditus
and they didn't pay taxes but now
et non modo dare tributum Caesari an non
they're making good by paying 130
ipsi erant 'faciens in aeris descriptione reddenda bona CXXX
million pounds yes no maybe as a
decies libras, quod sic non pro maybe
settlement maybe you know because
tu scis quod maybe colonia
cents on the dollar it doesn't sound i
Vocem non cents pupa
paid thirteen percent for everything i
I percent tredecim omnia solvit
buy that's canada for you eh but hey i'm
heus Im 'non te putas emere quod in Canada
sorry boo chi yeah on a plus side we
hinc plus dolet de boo memini chi
have maple syrup 24-7 pretty much yeah
acernus surrepo enim pulchra valde 24-7 yeah
365 we like we don't have to pay for
Ut et nos debemus pro CCCLXV non reddere
health care yep we can walk into a
ambulate in salutem cura possumus yep
hospital and just have a baby that's
et sicut infans quod haberet hospitium
what we we can it Canada's not that
Non enim possumus nos, quae est Canada scriptor
weird although it has been done without
Ridiculum est etiam sine
a whole other news story in the news
totam fabulam alius novus nuntius
this week I heard it on the category 5
Hoc septimana ego audivi quod genus in V
not TV newsrooms oh it must be true ah a
O TV newsrooms non oportet quod sit verum ah
new fan made half-life game is due to be
dimidium-vita novum fan factum est debitum ad ludum
released on Steam next month I'm excited
Vapor dimisit in proximo mense sum excitatur
about this yes prospect is made by 25
a quo etiam factum est circa XXV Prospectus
year old indie developer Richard
Richard annus vetus elit indie
Seabrook I can pronounce that name
Seabrook pronunciare possum, quod nomen,
anyway who two years ago decided to quit
quis usquam voluit quit duos annos
his job and make the game as a job
facere ludum quod eius officium, et a officium
application and valve the company behind
applicationem in turba et post valvae
half life has given Seabrook approval to
media ad vitam dedit Seabrook approbatione
use graphics and assets from half-life 2
dimidium-vita II graphics et de usu bonorum
and while the game is not an official
et dum ludum est non officialis
half-life title it has been approved by
dimidium-vita probatus est in illo titulo
the company nice two weeks ago we
societatem habemus eu duo weeks ago
reported a story about Pembroke Ontario
nuntiavit fabulam de Penbrok Ontario
father who's 70 year old son ran up an
quis pater LXX natus annos et filii procurrens
Xbox bill totaling over eight thousand
Octo milia litteras Xbox totalling
dollars and now Microsoft has given him
et nunc dollars Microsoft tradidit eum
a refund for the full amount which is
quae est plena moles a ad refugium
what yeah so let's / good on him like no
ita quod yeah lets '/ bonam ut in eo non est
Lance Perkins said he was stunned to
Perkins lance dictum erat ad somno evigilans
discover charges on his credit card bill
fidem card in sua libellum invenire criminibus
in December and criticized the company
in December, et animadversum societatem
for what he called a misleading business
nam dicitur quod rem caecam
scheme Perkins complained Microsoft and
Perkins Microsoft et ratio quereretur
the company agreed to look into the
constat spectare ad societatem
charges he says microsoft initially told
Microsoft initio inultum abire dicit ei
him it couldn't refund the money when
non illi reddet pecuniam
the company learned perkins son was a
Perkins Filius didicit erat in turba
minor it agreed to refund the full
constat ad plenum quod minor est reddet emptori
amount of eight thousand two hundred and
Syracusanis octo milium numerum ducentorum
six dollars and 43 cents and in a
et intra sex pupa XLIII cents
statement Microsoft responded by saying
Microsoft dicitur respondit dicens
Microsoft may occasionally choose to
Microsoft ut eligere ad occasionally
provide a one-time refund in cases of
provide autem de uno-vicis refugium in casibus,
minors making purchases without parental
emptionibus minorum sine parentum
permission they also made it clear
Et sic manifestum est quod permission
though that those refunds are for very
quamquam id illi non de ipso refunds
small number of users in exceptional
exceptis paucis users
cases and it will only be granted once
simul et casibus non solum reddent
in a lifetime Perkins is surprised by
mirum est tecum in vita
Microsoft's response and hopes that his
Microsoft scriptor responsio et exspectationes, quas eius
story will help protect other parents
historia se defendat auxiliatus sum parentes
and warn them how online gaming bills
et monere eos ut bills online forumque aleatoruml
can add up
addere possit ascendere
big facts this week to sr wences and RW
R. Et facta est magnus septem sr wences
nash and our community of viewers for
Nash et civitas ex nobis nam viewers
submitting stories to us if you found a
si subditi fabulas condas
new story you'd like to send email it's
fabulae velis mittere email suus
a newsroom at category five dot TV for
in TV et dat quinque newsroom ad genus
all your tech news with a slight linux
fama tua doce levi Linux
bias visit category 5 TV news room at
V genus pondus visit cubiculum at TV News
newsroom category 5 TV for the category
V TV newsroom genus ad genus
5 TV news room i'm jeff weston
V locus nuntium TV sum Jeff weston